Washington and Lee University and Regional Virginia History Research Collection WLU.Coll.0668
Washington and Lee University, University Library Special Collections and Archives
- Buffalo Forge (Box 11, Folder 10)
  Virginia -- Buffalo Forge
- Buildings (Box 11, Folder 11-12)
  Buildings
  - McCrum's Drug Store (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Rockbridge County Courthouse (Box 11, Folder 12)
    Virginia -- Rockbridge County; Virginia -- Buena Vista; Courthouses
- Calfpasture Rivers (Box 11, Folder 13)
  Calf Pasture River
- Canals (Box 11, Folder 14-15)
  Canals
  - Canals (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - James River and Kanawha (Box 11, Folder 15)
    Canals; Virginia -- James River and Kanawha Canal
- Cedar Grove (Box 11, Folder 16)
  Virginia -- Cedar Grove
- Cemeteries (Box 11, Folder 17-18)
  Cemeteries
  - Pilson (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Cemeteries: Tinkling Springs (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Centerville Community, Lexington, Virginia (Box 11, Folder 19)
  Virginia -- Lexington
- Churches (Box 11, Folder 20-30)
  - Buena Vista (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Cedar Hill (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Falling Springs (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Grace Episcopal Church (Box 11, Folder 23)
    R. E. Lee Memorial Episcopal Church (Lexington, Va.); Grace Memorial Church (Lexington, Va.)
  - Haines Chapel (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Lexington Presbyterian Church (Box 11, Folder 25)
    Lexington Presbyterian Church (Lexington, Va.)
  - Mt. Zion (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - New Monmouth Presbyterian (Box 11, Folder 27)
    New Monmouth Presbyterian Church (Lexington, Va.)
  - Poplar Hill (Box 11, Folder 28)
    Poplar Hill
  - Timber Ridge (Box 11, Folder 29)
    Timber Ridge Presybterian Church (Lexington, Va.)
  - Tinkling Springs (Box 11, Folder 30)
- Circus (Box 12, Folder 1)
  Circus
- Civil War (Box 12, Folder 2-9)
  Civil war
  - Bible Society (Box 12, Folder 2)
    Civil war; Bible Society of the Confederate States
  - General (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Lexington, VA (Box 12, Folder 4)
    Virginia -- Lexington; Civil war
  - Religion (Box 12, Folder 5)
    Religion; Christianity; Civil war
  - Rockbridge Artillery, First (Box 12, Folder 6)
    Civil war; Confederate States of America. Army. Virginia Artillery. Rockbridge Battery, 1st (1861-1865)
  - Rockbridge County, Virginia (Box 12, Folder 7)
    Virginia -- Rockbridge County; Virginia -- Lexington
  - Rockbridge Dragoons (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Veterans (Box 12, Folder 9)
    Veterans; Civil war
- Coffee (Box 12, Folder 10)
  Coffee
- Collierstown, Virginia (Box 12, Folder 11)
  Virginia -- Collierstown
- Companies (Box 12, Folder 12-13)
  - Saddle and Harness (Box 12, Folder 12)
    Saddle and Harness Company
  - Power-Hadson Development (Box 12, Folder 13)
    Hadson Development Corporation
- Cornwall, Virginia (Box 12, Folder 14)
  Virginia -- Cornwall
- Correspondence: Roosevelt, Theodore (copy) (Box 12, Folder 15)
  Roosevelt, Theodore
- Declaration of Independence (Box 12, Folder 16)
  Declaration of Independence
- Deeds (Box 12, Folder 17-18)
  Deeds
  - Deeds: McDowell, Ephriam (Box 12, Folder 17)
    McDowell, Ephriam, 1672-1775
  - Deeds: Vance, Samuel (Box 12, Folder 18)
    Vance, Samuel
- Deerfield, Virginia (Box 12, Folder 19)
  Virginia -- Deerfield
- English Speaking Union (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Envelopes (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Farms (Box 12, Folder 22-23)
  Farms
  - Alpine (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Sunnyside Farm, 8 pages (Box 12, Folder 23)
    Sunnyside Farm
- Forks of the James (Box 12, Folder 24)
  Virginia -- James River
- Foundations (Box 12, Folder 25-26)
  - Marshall (Box 12, Folder 25)
    Foundations
  - Virginia Horse Center (Box 12, Folder 26)
    Includes writing ink pen marked, Virginia Horse Center, Honoring Gov. Charles S. Robb, Bill Signing Day, March 22, 1985.
    Virginia Horse Center
- Freedmen's Bureau (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Frontier Culture Museum (Box 12, Folder 28)
  Frontier Culture Museum
- Genealogy (Box 13, Box 13-15, Folder 4)
  Genealogy
  - Ailstock Family (Box 13, Folder 1)
    Ailstock Family
  - Alexander Family (Box 13, Folder 2)
    Alexander family
  - Alford Family (Box 13, Folder 3)
    Alford Family
  - Anderson Family (Box 13, Folder 4)
    Anderson family
  - Black Family (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Blair Family (Box 13, Folder 6)
    Blair family
  - Borden Family (Box 13, Folder 7)
    Borden family
  - Brockenbrough Family (Box 13, Folder 8)
    Brockenbrough family
  - Broun Family (Box 13, Folder 9)
    Broun family
  - Brubeck Family (Box 13, Folder 10)
    Brubeck family
  - Cunningham Family (Box 13, Folder 11)
    Cunningham family
  - Custis Family (Box 13, Folder 12)
    Custis family
  - Debo Family (Box 13, Folder 13)
    Debo family
  - Dold Family (Box 13, Folder 14)
    Dold family
  - Doremus Family (Box 13, Folder 15)
    Doremus Family
  - Edmiston Family (Box 13, Folder 16)
    Edmiston family
  - Elliott Family (Box 13, Folder 17)
    Elliott Family
  - Fix Family (Box 13, Folder 18)
    Fix Family
  - Gaines Family (Box 13, Folder 19)
    Gaines Family
  - Harer Family (Box 13, Folder 20)
    Harer family
  - Harman Family (Box 13, Folder 21)
    Harman family
  - Houston Family (Box 13, Folder 22)
    Houston family
  - Hughes Family (Box 13, Folder 23)
    Hughes family
  - Johnston Family (Box 13, Folder 24)
    Johnston family
  - Jordan Family (Box 13, Folder 25)
    Jordan Family
  - Kahle Family (Box 13, Folder 26)
    Kahle Family
  - Link Family (Box 13, Folder 27)
    Link family
  - Livingston Family (Box 13, Folder 28)
    Livingston family
  - McAfee Family (Box 14, Folder 1)
    McAfee family
  - McClintic Family (Box 14, Folder 2)
    McClintic family
  - McCown Family (Box 14, Folder 3)
    McCown family
  - McFarland Family (Box 14, Folder 4)
    McFarland family
  - Mohler Family (Box 14, Folder 5)
    Mohler family
  - Morrison Family (Box 14, Folder 6)
    Morrison family
  - Moore Family (Box 14, Folder 7)
    Moore Family
  - Obenshain Family (Box 14, Folder 8)
    Obenshain family
  - Paul Family (Box 14, Folder 9)
    Paul family
  - Preston Family (Box 14, Folder 10)
    Preston family
  - Rees Family (Box 14, Folder 11)
    Rees Family
  - Rhea Family (Box 14, Folder 12)
    Rhea family
  - Richey Family (Box 14, Folder 13)
    Richey family
  - Salling Family (Box 14, Folder 14)
    Salling Family
  - Scott Family (Box 14, Folder 15)
    Scott family
  - Shaw Family (Box 14, Folder 16)
    Shaw family
  - Sherrard Family (Box 14, Folder 17)
    Sherrard Family
  - Singleton Family (Box 14, Folder 18)
    Singleton Family
  - Stuart Family (Box 14, Folder 19)
    Stuart family
  - Waddell Family (Box 14, Folder 20)
    Waddell family
  - Warner Family (Box 14, Folder 21)
    Warner family
  - Washington Family (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Watts Family (Box 14, Folder 23)
    Watts family
  - Whitlock Family (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Whitlock Family
  - Willson Family (Box 15, Folder 2)
    Willson Family
  - Wood Family (Box 15, Folder 3)
    Wood family
  - Young Family (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Young Family
- Glasgow, Virginia (Box 15, Folder 5)
  Virginia -- Glasgow
- Goshen Pass, Virginia (Box 15, Folder 6)
  Virginia -- Goshen Pass
- Goshen, Virginia, 1896 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  Virginia -- Goshen
- Green Pastures (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Historic Lexington Foundation (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Horses (Box 15, Folder 10-11)
  - "Little Sorrel" (Box 15, Folder 10)
    Stonewall Jackson's war horse.
    Little Sorrel (Horse)
  - "Traveller" and "Lucy Long" (Box 15, Folder 11)
    General R. E. Lee's War-Horses, Traveller and Lucy Long. Southern Historical Society Papers. Vol.18. Richmond, Va., January-December, 1890.
    Traveller (Horse); Lucy Long (Horse)
- Hospitals (Box 15, Folder 12-13)
  Hospitals
  - Dejarnette, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    Hospitals; Dejarnette Center
  - Stonewall Jackson Memorial (Box 15, Folder 13)
    Includes 1952 pay schedules for Registered Nurses at Jackson Memorial Hospital.
    Hospitals; Stonewall Jackson Hospital Auxiliary Inc.; Stonewall Jackson Memorial Hospital
- Hotels (Box 15, Folder 14-16)
  Hotels
  - Lexington, VA (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Robert E. Lee Hotel (Box 15, Folder 15)
    Hotels; Robert E. Lee Hotel
  - Rockbridge County's Boom (Box 15, Folder 16)
- House Mountain, 1839; Ruffner, Henry, Reverend; 1 Item (Box 15, Folder 17)
  The Student's Account of His Visit to the House Mountain. The Height of Our Mountains by John Elder
  House Mountain. Rockbridge County, Virginia
  - House Mountain Inn flyer and information on rooms and rates.
    House Mountain Inn
- Houses (Box 15, Folder 18-38)
  - Alexander, William (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Arlington (Box 15, Folder 19)
    Virginia--Arlington
  - Belfield, 1 Item (Box 15, Folder 19A)
    Dwelling in Lexington, Virginia, designed by Pendleton Scott Clark, architecture renowned for authenticity, was completed in 1929 for W&L Dean and Mrs. Frank J. Gilliam. The handsome gardens for the Gilliams were primarily designed by the Charles Gillette, a widely regarded landscape architect of Richmond, Virginia.
    Gilliam, Frank Johnson; Clark, Pendleton Scott; Gillette, Charles
  - Blandome (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Buffalo Springs Farms (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Clifton (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Col Alto (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Dold (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Dungeness (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Irish Gap Inns (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Lee-Jackson at Washington and Lee (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Leyburn (Box 15, Folder 28)
    Leyburn family
  - Mackey, John (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Miller-Kite (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Moore, John (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Mountain View Farm (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Oak Ridge Estate (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Roseneath (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Savernake (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Stone Cottage (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Stonewall (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Stonewall Jackson House (Box 15, Folder 38)
- Hull's Drive-In (Box 16, Folder 1)
  Hull's Drive-In
- Indians (Box 16, Folder 2-4)
  - The Creek Nation (Box 16, Folder 2)
    Creek Indians
  - Kerr's Creek (Box 16, Folder 3)
    Virginia -- Kerr's Creek
  - Monacan (Box 16, Folder 4)
    Monacan Indians
- Inns (Box 16, Folder 5-6)
  - Hummingbird (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Sheridan Livery (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Iron Industry: Rockbridge Co., VA (Box 16, Folder 7)
  Virginia -- Rockbridge County; Iron Industry and Trade
- James River (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Jordan's Point (Box 16, Folder 9)
  Virginia -- Lexington -- Jordan's Point
- Lakes: Cave Mountain (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Land Grants (Box 16, Folder 11-12)
  - Beverley (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Borden (Box 16, Folder 12)
    Virginia -- Benjamin Borden Grant
- Lee-Jackson Day (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Lexington Rockbridge Studio Tour, 2016-05-14-2017-05-14; 2 Item (Box 16, Folder 14)
  Virginia--Rockbridge County--Artists
- Lexington, VA (Box 16, Folder 15-22)
  - Ghosts (Box 16, Folder 15)
    Virginia -- Lexington; Ghosts
  - History (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - History - "Sommersby" (Box 16, Folder 17)
    Sommersby (Motion picture); Virginia -- Lexington
  - Lexington, VA (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Police Department (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Stonegate Colonial Homes (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Theatre (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Women (Box 16, Folder 22)
    Women; Virginia -- Lexington
- Libraries: Rockbridge Regional (Box 16, Folder 23)
  Virginia -- Lexington; Rockbridge Regional Library (Lexington, Va.)
- Lost River State Park (West Virginia), 1 Files (Box 16, Folder 24)
  History of the Lost River State Park. A part of this park was formerly known as Lee White Sulphur Spring or Howard's Lick. Also included is a history of the Lee Cabin, whithin the park in Hardy County, West Virginia.
  West Virginia--Howard's Lick; West Virginia--Lost River State Park; West Virginia--Lee White Sulphur Spring; Lee, Carter
- Middlebrook, Virginia (Box 17, Folder 1)
  Virginia -- Middlebrook
- Middlesex County, VA (Box 17, Folder 2)
  Virginia -- Middlesex County
- Midway (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Miller's House Museum, 2015; 1 Item (Box 17, Folder 4)
  At Jordan's Point - Interpreting the Industrial and Transportation History of the Lexington, Virginia Area, Brochure
  Jordan's Point
- Mills (Box 17, Folder 5-9)
  - General (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Gilmore (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Osceola (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Wade's Mill (Box 17, Folder 8)
    Happy Holidays card from Wade's Mill, John and Karen Siegfried, 2017. Also included from 2017 are as follows: 7 postcards, brochure, information card, retail grain's price list, and a flyer listing the stone-ground grains available at Wade's Mill. Also, a December 2, 1992 News-Gazetter article on the history of the mill and it's owners at the time.
  - Woolen (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Mining Industry (Box 17, Folder 10-12)
  - Longdale Furnace (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Longdale, Virginia (Box 17, Folder 11)
    Virginia -- Longdale
  - Low Moor (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Mountain View (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Museums: American Frontier Culture (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Music (Box 17, Folder 15)
  Music
- Natural Bridge (Box 17, Folder 16-18)
  Virginia -- Natural Bridge
  - Engravings (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 17, Folder 17)
    Virginia -- Natural Bridge; Natural Bridge State Park
  - Safari Park (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Nature Trails (Box 17, Folder 19-21)
  Nature trails
  - Blue Ridge Parkway (Box 17, Folder 19)
    Nature trails; United States -- Blue Ridge Parkway
  - Chessie (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Woods Creek (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Newspapers (Box 17, Folder 22-24)
  Newspapers
  - Lexington Gazette (Box 17, Folder 22)
    Newspapers; Lexington Gazette. (Lexington, Va.)
  - Ring-tum Phi (Box 17, Folder 23)
    Ring-Tum Phi; Newspapers
  - The Wreath (Box 17, Folder 24)
- North River Covered Bridge (Box 17, Folder 25)
- Palmer Community Center (Box 17, Folder 26)
  Palmer Community Center
- Phi Beta Kappa (Box 17, Folder 27)
  Washington and Lee University. Phi Beta Kappa
- Postal Service: Letter Carriers (Box 17, Folder 28)
  Postal service
- Postmasters (Box 17, Folder 29)
  Postmasters
- Presbyterians: Women (Box 17, Folder 30)
  Presbyterian Church; Women
- Prince Edward County, Virginia (Box 17, Folder 31)
  Virginia--Prince Edward County
- Railroads (Box 17, Folder 32-36)
  Railroads
  - Baltimore & Ohio (Box 17, Folder 32)
    Railroads; Baltimore and Ohio Railroad Company
  - Chesapeake and Ohio (Box 17, Folder 33)
    Railroads; Chesapeake and Ohio Railway
  - National Railway Bulletin (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Railroads (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Virginia (Box 17, Folder 36)
    Railroads; Virginia
- Resorts (Box 18, Folder 1-2)
  Resorts
  - Sweet Chalybeate Springs (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Yellow Sulphur Springs (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Yellow Sulphur Springs Company
- Richmond, Virginia, 1958; 1 Item (Box 18, Folder 3)
  Clouds of Glory, A girl born in Richmond of Northern parents adopts Confederate loyalties, Virginia Cavalcade, Autumn
  Richmond, Virginia
- Roads (Box 18, Folder 4-5)
  Roads
  - Junction Valley Turnpike (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Turnpikes (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Robert E. Lee Residences, 2005; Hobbs, Patricia A.; 1 Item (Box 18, Folder 6)
  "An Ideal Home Circle": Lee Residences in Lexington, VA
  Washington and Lee University. Lee House. President's House
- Rockbridge County, Virginia (Box 18, Folder 7-19)
  Virginia -- Rockbridge County
  - Fine Arts (Box 18, Folder 7)
    Virginia -- Rockbridge County; Arts
  - Girls (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Government Officials, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    Virginia -- Rockbridge County; County government -- Officials and employees
  - History (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - History - Craftsmen (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Institutional Officials, 1998-1999; Washington and Lee University, Department of Journalism and Mass Communications (Box 18, Folder 12)
    Virginia -- Rockbridge County; Virginia -- Lexington; Local government -- Officials and employees
  - Maps and miscellaneous, 1938; 2017 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    Includes a Rockbridge County, Virginia road map from 1938 and a 2017 Lexingon/Rockbridge Chamber of Commerce community map which includes places and roads for the county as well as local business advertisements.
    Virginia -- Rockbridge County; Automobiles -- Road maps
  - United State Road Maps, Texaco, AAA, Esso, 1960-1970; 7 Item (Box 18, Folder 13A)
    Automobiles -- Road maps
  - Property Claims, 1782 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Seven Hills, Douty, Horace; 3 Item (Box 18, Folder 15)
    The Seven Hills of Rockbridge include the homes, Cherry Hill, Fruit Hill, Fancy Hill, Rose Hill, Hickory Hill, Clover Hill, and Liberty Hill. A map of the location of these homes is included, as well as descriptions from the Rockbridge County, Virginia Hertiage Book.
    Seven Hills. Rockbridge County, Virginia
  - Sketch, 1919 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Voter Facts, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    Virginia -- Rockbridge County; Voting
  - Women (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - World War II (Box 18, Folder 19)
    Christmas; World War (1939-1945)
- Schools (Box 18, Folder 20-31)
  Education; Virginia -- Rockbridge County
  - Buena Vista Colored (Box 18, Folder 20)
    Virginia -- Buena Vista; Schools
  - Cave Mountain (Box 18, Folder 21)
    Schools
  - Cross Roads (Box 18, Folder 22)
    Schools; Cross Roads School
  - Denmark School, 50th Anniversary of the closing of Denmark School, 1917-1943, Two newspaper articles, Denmark School reunion draws...170 people, September 24 & 30, 1992. Reunion group photo, 1993., 6 Item (Box 18, Folder 22A)
    Denmark School
  - Elizabeth College (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Goshen, Virginia (Box 18, Folder 24)
    Virginia -- Goshen; Schools; Goshen Business Men's League
  - Highland Belle (Box 18, Folder 25)
    Includes a one page Closing Exercises Program for June 1, 1950 and a report card for Mary Alphin.
    Schools; Highland Belle School
  - Lexington High, The Lexington High School newspaper - v.3, no.2, Nov. 20, 1924; v.4, no.4, Feb. 20, 1926; v.4, no.5, March 20, 1926; v.5, no.1, Oct. 20. 1926; v.5, no.2, Nov. 20, 1926; v.5, no.3, Dec. 20, 1926; v.5, no.5, March 22, 1927; and v.8, no.6, May 31, 1929. All a gift of Anne McClung. (Box 18, Folder 26)
    The Scarletter, Lexington High School newsletter - v.30 no.2, Oct. 31, 1977; v.30 no.7, April 8, 1978; v.30 no.8, May 3, 1978.
    Football Programs: Lexington vs. Turner Ashby, Sept. 27, 1974; Lexington vs. Harrisonburg, Oct. 11, 1974; Lexington vs. Broadway, Sept. 9, 1977.
    Schools; Lexington High School (Lexington, Va.); The Echo; The Scarletter
  - Liberty Hall Academy (Box 18, Folder 27)
    Schools; Liberty Hall Academy
  - Mountain View School (Box 18, Folder 28)
    Schools; Mountain View School
  - Palmer School and Community Center (Box 18, Folder 29)
    Schools; Palmer Community Center
  - Ruffner (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Southern Virginia College (Box 18, Folder 31)
    Education, Secondary; Schools; Southern Virginia College
- Scotch-Irish Congress (Box 19, Folder 1)
  Scotch Irish Congress
- Scrapbooks (Box 19, Folder 2-3)
  Scrapbooks
  - Agnew, Jean Cameron (Box 19, Folder 2)
    Scrapbooks; Agnew, Jean Cameron, 1877-1955
  - Lee, Mildred, Lee, Mildred Childe (Box 19, Folder 3)
    Scrapbooks; Lee, Robert E., General (Robert Edward)
- Shenandoah (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Societies (Box 19, Folder 5-6)
  Societies
  - Franklin Society (Box 19, Folder 5)
    Franklin Society and Library Company of Lexington (Lexington, Va.)
  - Rockbridge Colonization (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Speeches: ODK, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  Washington and Lee University. Omicron Delta Kappa
- Springs (Box 19, Folder 8-9)
  Springs
  - Warm (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Wilson's Springs (Box 19, Folder 9)
    Wilson's Springs
- Stables: Wright (Box 19, Folder 10)
  Stables
- Stores (Box 19, Folder 11-14)
  - The General Store (Box 19, Folder 11)
    Virginia -- Buena Vista; The General Store (1894 - ) (Buena Vista, VA)
  - Denmark General Store, News-Gazette article., 2002-07-03; 1 Item (Box 19, Folder 11A)
    Denmark Store
  - Kerr's Creek (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Rockbridge Baths, Irvine, Carrie M. (Box 19, Folder 13)
    Life in Late Nineteenth Century Rockbridge Baths, paper written at Hollins College, Ms. Mary W. Atwell, Carrie M. Irvine, [ca.1974].
    Virginia -- Rockbridge Baths
  - Walker and Wood Brothers (Box 19, Folder 14)
    Walker and Wood Brothers
- Timber Ridge (Box 19, Folder 15)
  Virginia -- Timber Ridge
- United Daughters of the Confederacy, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  United Daughters of the Confederacy. Rockbridge Chapter
- Valentine's Day (Box 19, Folder 17)
  Valentine's Day
- Vesuvius Ruritan Club (Box 19, Folder 18)
  Vesuvius Ruritan Club
- Virginia Military Institute (Box 19, Folder 19-22)
  Virginia Military Institute
  - VMI Barracks, 1850; Brockenbrough, John; 1 Item Photocopy (Box 19, Folder 19)
    Address Delivered by the Hon. John W. Brockenbrough on laying the corner stone of the new barracks of the Virginia Military Institute, July 4, 1850. New York: John Wiley, 1850.
  - Cameron Hall (Box 19, Folder 20)
    Virginia Military Institute. Cameron Hall
  - Football, 1937 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    Football; Virginia Military Institute; University of Maryland
  - Virginia Military Institute, 1964; 1998 (Box 19, Folder 22)
- Virginia Public Schools, 1901-11-17; Ruffner, William Henry; 1 Item (Box 19, Folder 23)
  Photocoy
  Virginia. Public Schools
- Washington Academy, 1803 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  Washington Academy (Lexington, Va.)
- Washington and Lee University (Box 19, Box 19-21, Folder 31)
  Washington and Lee University
  - Alumni (Box 19, Folder 25)
    Washington and Lee University; Washington and Lee University. Alumni
  - Architecture (Box 19, Folder 26)
    Architecture; Washington and Lee University
  - Art (Box 19, Folder 27)
    Art; Washington and Lee University
  - Band (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - African - American Students and History of Integration at W&L (Box 20, Folder 2)
    African American college students; Washington and Lee University
  - "Cadaver Bridge" or "Class Memorial Bridge" (Box 20, Folder 3)
    Bridges; Washington and Lee University
  - Catalogue, 1846-1847 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Charter (Box 20, Folder 5)
    Charters; Washington and Lee University
  - Cincinnati Society (Box 20, Folder 6)
    Society of the Cincinnati in the State of Virginia; Washington and Lee University
  - Civil War (Box 20, Folder 7)
    Civil war; Washington and Lee University
  - Coeducation (Box 20, Folder 8)
    Coeducation; Washington and Lee University
  - Coeducation Exhibit, 2014 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    Includes 1980's bumper sticker, "W&L Better Dead, Then Co-ed."
    Coeducation; Bumper stickers; Washington and Lee University
  - The Columns (Box 20, Folder 10)
    Washington and Lee University; The Columns
  - Comics, 2012; Reynolds, Patrick M; 1 Files (Box 20, Folder 11)
    FLASHBACK comic strips of Washington and Lee University history
    Washington and Lee University; Robinson, John; Washington College
  - Commencement (Box 20, Folder 12)
    Commencement ceremonies; Washington and Lee University
  - Concert Guild (Box 20, Folder 13)
    Washington and Lee University; Concert Guild
  - Course of Studies (Box 20, Folder 14)
    Education; Washington and Lee University
  - Crew Team, Lewis, Charles C.; 1 Item (Box 20, Folder 15)
    Charles C. Lewis, Jr. W&L '68, '71L; Charles C. Lewis, W&L 1930, M.A. 1931; H. Flood Madison, Jr., W&L 1920.
    A Tale of an Oar: A Hidden Message Revealed
  - Doremus Gym (Box 20, Folder 16)
    Washington and Lee University. Doremus Gymnasium; Washington and Lee University
  - Dormitories (Box 20, Folder 17)
    Dormitories; Washington and Lee University
  - Faculty (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Fashion, 1900; 1906 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    Fashion; Washington and Lee University
  - Fellowship Recipients, 1909-2004 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Football (Box 20, Folder 21)
    Football; Washington and Lee University. Department of Athletics. Football; Washington and Lee University
  - Founder's Day (Box 20, Folder 22)